

# nops **Lode**

Leuven, Belgium

□ (+32)486 62 50 78 | ■ bisschopslode@gmail.com | □ LodeBisschops | □ lode-bisschops

"Without data analytics, companies are blind and deaf, wandering out into the world like deer on a freeway."

### Summary.

Current student artificial intelligence at a top university, finishing in July 2022. I'm easy going and love to problem-solve challenging tasks, learn new technologies and interface with different departments. 2+ years of experience interpreting and analyzing data to drive successful business solutions. Excellent knowledge of analytics tools for effective analysis of data.

## Work Experience

**FibriCheck** Hasselt, Belgium DATA ANALYST Feb. 2020 - May 2022

• Created an automated data market using data pipelines and cloud computing infrastructure.

- · Constructed an interactive dashboard with visualisations and filters.
- Provided actionable insights and calculated key performance indicators.
- · Led my own project.
- In depth understanding of NoSQL data aggregation through research.
- Created complex data insights using Python and Jupyter notebooks.
- Interfaced with marketing to understand their needs.
- Clearly documented my work and educated colleagues at the end of my contract.
- Traineeship that turned into permanent employment with the firm.

**TeamHypeCoaching** Flanders, Belgium

STRENGTH COACH Nov. 2020 - Jun. 2021

- Built up a company with 2 friends, providing online strength coaching for 40 athletes.
- · Progress analysis using excel automation.

Le Notariat Westerlo, Belgium

WAITER AND HOSPITALITY Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2021

• Serving at a Gault & Millau selected cocktail bar, serving guests as a hospitable host.

#### Education

#### Katholieke Universiteit Leuven

Leuven, Belgium

MASTERS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE: ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

2020 - 2022

- · Belgium's highest-ranked university.
- · Completing degree in July.

#### **University of Hasselt**

Hasselt, Belgium

BACHELORS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

2016 - 2020

- In depth understanding of Python, Java, C++ and C.
- · Strong background in mathematics, statistics and software engineering.
- Familiar with: Prolog, Javascript, cloud based solutions, relational and non-relational databases.
- Familiar with the latest project management techniques.

#### Research\_

MASTER THESIS

#### **Exploring Deceptive affiliate Marketing within Facebook**

Leuven, Belgium

2021 - 2022

· Researching malicious advertisements within Facebook and how to detect them.

- Finding patterns within large datasets using SQL, Python and MongoDB.
- · Gathering data with web-scraping tools in remote containerized applications using Kubernetes.

APRIL 17, 2022 BISSCHOPS LODE · RÉSUMÉ

#### Aggregating Data for Statistical Analysis in MongoDB Atlas.

Hasselt, Belgium

Bachelor Thesis Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- Compared different database technologies for data aggregation.
- Explored different ways to aggregate data in an unstructured NoSQL database.
- Set up a real-time dashboard for basic performance indicators.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **Hermes - fraternity of economics**

Hasselt, Belgium

2019 - 2020

- Organised social events for new students.
- Assisted the job fair.

PLEDGEMASTER

· Participated in biweekly meetings.

#### References\_

Ine Van Loon, Marketing Manager, *FibriCheck*, ■ ine.vanloon@fibricheck.com Glenn De Witte, Data Science Manager, *FibriCheck*, ■ glenn.dewitte@fibricheck.com Guylian Menten, Owner, *Le Notariat*, □(+32) 493 13 73 88

Reference letters provided upon request.